morningledger.com 2018-09-09

# Privacy Policy - Morning Ledger

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998). Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

 **The Information We Collect**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the morningledger.com. On some pages, make requests, and register to receive music,ecards, etc. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name

Address

Email address

Friend’s e-mail addresses (Tell-A-Friend contest)

 **How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?**

We use Web site browser software tools such as cookies and Web server logs to gather information about our Web site users’ browsing activities, in order to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. This information assists us to design and arrange our Web pages in the most user-friendly manner and to continually improve our Web site to better meet the needs of our customers and prospective customers. Cookies help us collect important business and technical statistics. The information in the cookies lets us trace the paths followed by users to our Web site as they move from one page to another. Web server logs allow us to count how many people visit our Web site and evaluate our Web site’s visitor capacity. We do not use these technologies to capture your individual email address or any personally identifying information about you although they do permit us to send focused online banner advertisements or other such responses to you.

 **The Way We Use Information**

We do not share your information with outside parties. We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an request only for the tell-a-friend contest. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive for tech support, customer service, tell-a-friend contest, email updates and to send registered users their unlock codes. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

 **Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

 **Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

 **Third-Party Websites**

This website may provide links to third-party websites. Any such links are provided solely as a convenience to you. morningledger.com has no control over these websites or their content and does not assume any responsibility or liability for these websites. morningledger.com does not endorse or make any representations about these websites, or any information, materials, or products found thereon. If you access any of the third-party websites linked on this Web site, you do so at your own risk.

 **Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, www.morningledger.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**

www.morningledger.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.morningledger.com.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.morningledger.com and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – [www.google.com](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.morningledger.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.morningledger.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.morningledger.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

 **How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

At any time, you may later review or update the personal information we have collected online from you by contacting us at morningledger.com

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

 **How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email from our contactus page.
